Bruno Lucattelli

Software Developer

Mobile: +5511999552446 E-mail: <u>lucattelli@gmail.com</u> Github: /lucattelli

About

Software Developer since 2003, mainly working on software development projects for the enterprise segment. Vast experience in the SAP technology stack while also having a few projects being developed using different stacks. I already have experience working as a developer, a team lead and software architect. I'm an autodidact who also likes to share knowledge with my peers and with the developer community. In Brazil, I dedicated my spare time to help develop the local SAP community, organizing, speaking and attending events since 2009. I was nominated SAP Mentor and was part of the program from 2014 to 2018. I am dedicated and I learn fast.

After 15 years working in SAP consulting companies, I am looking for an opportunity outside this market segment. I'm looking for a technology company that is based on current software development best practices, cloud, devops and AI.

Professional Experience

 Technical Lead SAP and RPA at Cyrius do Brasil (jan/19 - current)
ABAP, JS, HANA, Fiori, SAPUIS, SCP, Node.js, UiPath

 Software Developer & SAP Tech Architect at Cyrius do Brasil (nov/16 - dec/18)
ABAP, JS, HANA, Fiori, SAPUI5, SCP, Node.js, SMP, Agentry, Workflow

 Software Developer & SAP Tech Architect at Tech Mahindra Brasil (mar/16 - oct/16)
ABAP, Fiori, SMP

 SAP Software Developer at Raízen Energia (oct/12 - feb/16)
ABAP, Kanban, JS, Design Patterns

 Software Developer & SAP Tech Architect at Go-Live IT Solutions (sep/06 – sep/12)
ABAP, Aqile, Kanban, XP, ASP.NET, C#, SAP PI, TDD, Design Patterns

 SAP ABAP Consultant at Braxis IT Services (jan/06 - aug/06)
ABAP, ASP.NET, C#

 SAP ABAP Consultant at Pimentel IT Services (nov/04 - dec/05)
ABAP, ASP.NET, C#, VBA, ASP, Workflow, SAP PI

 Support Analyst & Software Developer at Hi Soluções (apr/03 - oct/04)
Linux, PHP, VB 6.0, ASP, Delphi, VBA

 Instructor & Technical Coordinator at SOS Computadores (apr/01 - mar/03)

Other Experiences

- Speaker and organizer in several technology events for the local community 2009 current
- SAP Official Courses Instructor at SAP Education Brazil 2017 - current
- Nominated SAP Mentor 2014 - 2018
- Nominated SAP Developer Hero 2016

Technical Skills

- **Programming Languages:** ABAP, Javascript, Python, Java, PHP, C#, VB, VBA
- Web: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Node.js, Bootstrap
- Microsoft: Windows, Office, .NET Framework
- Databases: SAP HANA, Oracle DB, SQL Server, MySQL, MongoDB
- Al: Neural Networks, Linear Regression, Logistic Regression, Chatbots
- Computer Science & Software Engineering: OOP, Virtualization, Containers, DVCS, Open Source, Digital Transformation, SOA, Systems integration, Microservices, Enterprise Mobility, Design Patterns, TDD, Documentation
- Methodologies: Agile, XP, SCRUM, Kanban, PMBoK
- SAP: ABAP, HANA, Gateway, Web IDE, SCP, CDS, AMDP, BOPF, ABAP Channels, Workflow, SAPUI5/OpenUI5, Agentry, SMP, SLT, Data Aging, SAP Web Dispatcher
- Consulting: Presales, Presentations, Teaching, Hands-on Workshops

Education

 Anhembi Morumbi University – Business Administration 2019 – 2022

• FIAP – Systems Analysis and Development 2017 - 2018

Languages

- Brazilian Portuguese (native)
- English (fluent)
- Italian (basic)